Deck the halls, dodge the bad guys.
The Family Plan 2 is a action, comedy film directed by Simon Cellan Jones.
Now that Dan's assassin days are behind him, all he wants
for Christmas is quality time with his kids.
But when he learns his daughter has her own plans, he books a family trip to
London—putting them all in the crosshairs of an unexpected enemy.
Dan Morgan, played by Mark Wahlberg.
Jessica Morgan, played by Michelle Monaghan.
Finn Clarke, played by Kit Harington.
Nina Morgan, played by Zoe Colletti.
Kyle Morgan, played by Van Crosby.
Max Morgan, played by Theodore Lindsey.
The Family Plan 2 is a 2025 American action comedy film that is a sequel to the 2023 film The Family Plan with Mark Wahlberg,
Michelle Monaghan, Zoe Colletti, and Van Crosby reprising their roles and with Kit Harington also starring.
The film is directed by Simon Cellan Jones and written by David Coggeshall.
It was produced by Apple Studios and distributed
on Apple TV on November 21, 2025.
The tone is lighthearted.